[Script Info]
; // None
Title:K-ON
Original Script:None
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:848
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: zhengwenJP,DFGMaruGothic-Md,27,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H0027415C,&H9027415C,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,1,2,30,30,18,1
Style: zhengwen,方正准圆_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H0027415C,&H9027415C,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,1,2,30,30,13,134
Style: OPJ,MS Gothic,25,&H00FEFEFE,&H0000FFFF,&H11222222,&H11222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,8,85,85,11,128
Style: OPC,方正黑体_GBK,29,&H00FEFEFE,&H0000FFFF,&H11222222,&H11222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,76,76,8,134
Style: zhushiJP,DFGMaruGothic-Md,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H0027415C,&H9027415C,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,1,8,15,15,17,1
Style: zhushi,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H0027415C,&H9027415C,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,1,8,15,15,12,134
Style: EDJ,MS Gothic,25,&H00FEFEFE,&H0000FFFF,&H11222222,&H11222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,8,85,85,11,128
Style: EDC,方正黑体_GBK,29,&H00FEFEFE,&H0000FFFF,&H11222222,&H11222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,76,76,8,134
Style: EDJ2,MS Gothic,25,&H00010101,&H0000FFFF,&H11EEEEEE,&H11222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,8,85,85,11,128
Style: EDC2,方正黑体_GBK,29,&H00010101,&H0000FFFF,&H11EEEEEE,&H11222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,76,76,8,134
Style: title,方正准圆_GBK,32,&H00000000,&H0000FFFF,&H0027415C,&H9027415C,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,180,134
Style: title2,方正准圆_GBK,45,&H20EEEEEE,&H0000FFFF,&H20000000,&H80000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,21,30,140,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
; // JP
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.29,0:00:33.78,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お姉ちゃん  そろそろ起きないと…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.38,0:00:35.10,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お姉ちゃ…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.49,0:00:43.77,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はッ ８時！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.96,0:00:45.24,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちッ 遅刻 遅刻ッ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.37,0:00:46.27,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何で急ぐの？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.36,0:00:59.67,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちこく～ッ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.99,0:01:04.23,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あら 唯ちゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.38,0:01:05.43,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おはよ～
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.57,0:01:39.70,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あれ？ 見間違えた～
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.72,0:01:50.68,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今日から…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.60,0:01:53.89,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高校生！

Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.12,0:03:30.96,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,入学おめでとうございま～す
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.31,0:03:32.46,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ぜひ テニス部へ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.75,0:03:34.26,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ぜひ 柔道部へ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.47,0:03:35.46,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ぜひ 茶道部へ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.67,0:03:36.53,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ぜひ 珠算部へ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.84,0:03:37.79,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ぜひの ぜひ！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.75,0:04:00.26,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何うなってるのよ 唯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.38,0:04:02.91,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あッ 和ちゃ～ん
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.19,0:04:05.55,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,実はどの部活に入ろうか迷って…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.61,0:04:07.20,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,えッ まだ決めてなかったの？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.52,0:04:10.65,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もう 学校始まってから２週間も たってるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.79,0:04:13.25,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でもでも 私 運動オンチだし
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.50,0:04:16.38,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,文化系のクラブもよく分かんないし
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.08,0:04:20.64,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こうやってニートが出来上がっていくのね
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.96,0:04:23.17,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,部活やってないだけでニート!?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.55,0:04:24.70,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,振り返ってみると
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.01,0:04:28.31,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯って今まで 何の部活もやってこなかったもんね
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.39,0:04:28.31,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ニー…ニー…ニー…ト…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.69,0:04:29.23,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,グサッ！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.32,0:04:33.25,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何かしなくちゃ いけないような気がするんだけど…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.34,0:04:38.10,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一体 何をすればいいんだろ～う
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.99,0:04:50.19,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,澪～ッ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.83,0:04:51.54,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,律
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.67,0:04:53.11,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,クラブ見学 行こうぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.41,0:04:54.51,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,クラブ見学？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.83,0:04:56.69,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,軽音部だよ 軽音部
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.12,0:04:59.96,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でも私 文芸部に入るつもりだし
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.12,0:05:00.62,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,えッ？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.76,0:05:02.72,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,入部希望の紙も書いたし
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.70,0:05:06.50,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ビリッ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.84,0:05:09.14,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああーッ 何すんのよ 律！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.11,0:05:11.89,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ほ～ら 行くぞ 早く早く～
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.19,0:05:13.49,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと～
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.10,0:05:17.13,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,えッ 廃部した？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.22,0:05:20.34,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正確には 廃部寸前ね
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.72,0:05:23.81,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨年度までいた部員はみんな卒業しちゃって
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.59,0:05:28.26,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今月中に４人 入部しないと 廃部になっちゃうの
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.66,0:05:31.80,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だから 誰もいなかったんだ 音楽室
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.16,0:05:33.32,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生～
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.43,0:05:36.15,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はい 今 行くわね
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.58,0:05:39.49,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ごめんね 次 音楽の授業あるから
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.70,0:05:42.95,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,頑張ってね 軽音部
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.36,0:05:46.17,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,キレイな先生だったなあ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.36,0:05:47.77,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そういう問題じゃねえ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.63,0:05:54.87,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,このプリントをみんなに配っておいてね
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.86,0:05:59.64,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,プリントを…？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.74,0:06:02.31,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あッ は はい 失礼いたしやした
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.56,0:06:08.73,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,にらまれたッ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.33,0:06:10.24,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,テンポ悪…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.72,0:06:12.39,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,しッ しまった
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.43,0:06:13.46,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使えない子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.77,0:06:15.30,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すッ すみません
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.87,0:06:16.93,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大丈夫？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.83,0:06:20.91,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ドジっ子…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.25,0:06:25.91,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,廃部なら しかたないな
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.29,0:06:27.85,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私は文芸部に…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.32,0:06:30.92,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰も いないってことは
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.03,0:06:33.77,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今 入部すれば 私が部長？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.83,0:06:36.20,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,悪くないわね～
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.63,0:06:40.46,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの さっき話してた軽音部って？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.90,0:06:41.88,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,軽音部？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.08,0:06:43.17,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,って何ですか？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.63,0:06:46.19,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「軽い音楽」と書いて「軽音」よ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.73,0:06:49.04,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,軽い… 音楽？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.66,0:06:51.69,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そう 軽い音楽
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.77,0:07:00.50,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,で どうするの？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.97,0:07:02.66,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,入部希望者を待つ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.02,0:07:03.71,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待つの？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.95,0:07:04.87,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待つ！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.23,0:07:05.88,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うんッ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.07,0:07:20.06,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帰ろっか
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.08,0:07:24.24,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの～ 見学したいんですけど
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.64,0:07:25.67,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おおッ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.37,0:07:28.35,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,軽音部の？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.58,0:07:30.03,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いえ 合唱部の
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.29,0:07:32.02,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,軽音部に入りませんか？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.55,0:07:33.95,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの 合唱部に
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.03,0:07:35.85,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今 部員が少なくて
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.24,0:07:38.70,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お願いします 後悔は させません
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.22,0:07:41.99,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そんな強引な勧誘したら 迷惑だろッ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.14,0:07:45.83,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃあ 私も行くから
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.12,0:07:46.84,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,澪ッ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.60,0:07:53.22,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あのときの約束は…ウソだったのか！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.70,0:07:57.14,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私がドラムで 澪がベースで
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.48,0:08:04.99,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ずっと… ずっと 一緒にバンド組もうねって
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.86,0:08:08.13,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,約束… してたじゃないッ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.46,0:08:12.35,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,２人でライブに行った あの日
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.97,0:08:15.05,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これだ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.62,0:08:17.81,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これ… だよね
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.96,0:08:22.68,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あのときの言葉は ウソだったのかあ～ッ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.87,0:08:24.29,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その回想がウソだ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.46,0:08:25.99,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ありッ そうだっけ？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.60,0:08:29.79,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これだよ これッ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.18,0:08:32.47,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,バンドやろうよ バンド！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.53,0:08:35.16,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,て 律が強引に
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.38,0:08:37.01,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,澪も やるって言ったじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.38,0:08:38.45,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうだけど…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.85,0:08:40.29,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それで プロになったら
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.47,0:08:42.30,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ギャラは７：３ねって
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.42,0:08:43.39,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ねつ造すんな
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.81,0:08:50.48,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何だか 楽しそうですね
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.75,0:08:52.89,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,キーボードくらいしかできませんけど
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.24,0:08:55.64,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私で よければ 入部させてください
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.68,0:08:57.83,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ありがとーう
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.05,0:09:00.77,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これであと１人 入部すれば～
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.94,0:09:03.03,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私も もう人数に入ってるのね
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.12,0:09:04.56,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,えっと～
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.71,0:09:06.71,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琴吹紬です
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.04,0:09:08.44,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ドラムの田井中律
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.84,0:09:10.77,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こっちはベースの秋山澪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.30,0:09:13.01,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うん あとは…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.16,0:09:14.31,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ギターだな！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.28,0:09:19.01,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.74,0:09:21.82,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せっかく高校に入ったんだもん
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.10,0:09:23.69,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何か したいよね
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.91,0:09:25.13,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うん すれば
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.06,0:09:30.28,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でも 何したらいいか分かんないんだよ～
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.52,0:09:32.57,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やれやれ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.90,0:09:37.13,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ご一緒に ポテトも いかがですか？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.41,0:09:40.37,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はい お願いいたします
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.48,0:09:41.65,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ありがとうございます
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.57,0:09:46.26,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どした？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.53,0:09:49.61,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私 ファーストフードのお店 初めてで
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.89,0:09:50.70,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうなの!?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.23,0:09:53.68,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「ご一緒にポテトも いかがですか？」って言われるの
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.98,0:09:55.48,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あこがれてたんです
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.32,0:09:59.28,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すみません 始めてください
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.27,0:10:02.20,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よし 作戦会議 開始！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.70,0:10:05.58,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今月中に 部員をあと１人 獲得するために
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.89,0:10:07.31,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一体 何を？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.67,0:10:10.18,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それをこれから考えるのさあ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.86,0:10:11.80,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今 入部したら
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.12,0:10:14.51,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何か すんごい特典もらえるとか
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.76,0:10:15.62,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特典…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.94,0:10:17.77,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そう 何か もらえるとか
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.22,0:10:21.36,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,車とか 別荘… とかですか？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.68,0:10:23.17,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すごいけど 無理
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.54,0:10:24.44,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,アイス おごるとか
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.66,0:10:25.90,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宿題 手伝うとか
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.30,0:10:28.16,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そんなことで入部するとは…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.50,0:10:29.80,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃあ どうしたら
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.16,0:10:38.10,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ニョロリ～ン
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.56,0:10:40.31,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自分が飽きて どうする
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.60,0:10:42.79,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃあ 何か考えてよ～
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.25,0:10:45.28,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あッ もう帰りたい
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.74,0:10:48.01,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの～ とりあえず…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.83,0:10:49.75,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せ～の
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.81,0:11:00.29,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もう４月も あと１週間
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.07,0:11:02.89,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰も来てくれませんね
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.74,0:11:05.47,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,バンドも組めずに廃部か
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.91,0:11:08.02,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それは絶対 イヤーッ！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.82,0:11:18.13,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,軽…音楽か
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.89,0:11:27.51,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯ちゃん 上手ね
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.16,0:11:34.21,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よしッ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.98,0:11:39.19,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,けいおん！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.63,0:11:43.59,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,とりあえず 軽音楽部ってところに入ってみました
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.45,0:11:47.04,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,で どんなことするの？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.53,0:11:48.19,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,さあ？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.99,0:11:52.04,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でも 軽い音楽って書くから
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.26,0:11:54.40,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,きっと簡単なことしか やらないよ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.03,0:11:56.23,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,口笛とか
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.71,0:11:58.73,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何 その やる気のないクラブ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.46,0:12:03.36,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ほら 何かバンドとか するみたいだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.34,0:12:06.21,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私 ギターなんて弾けないよ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.70,0:12:08.57,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃあ 何なら弾けるの？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.55,0:12:13.95,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,カッ カスタネット
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.02,0:12:20.71,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すごく似合うわ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.04,0:12:22.04,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ほら これがさ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.20,0:12:22.95,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なあ あんたねッ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.35,0:12:24.25,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こんにちは
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.64,0:12:26.93,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こんにちは～
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.11,0:12:28.76,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,入部希望者がいたわよ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.48,0:12:32.45,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よかったわね
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.12,0:12:35.45,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それと ステキなティーセットだけど
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.71,0:12:37.48,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飲み終わったら ちゃんと片づけてね
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.00,0:12:39.38,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,は～い
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.16,0:12:44.32,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ヨッシャー 廃部じゃなくなる～
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.87,0:12:46.20,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平沢唯
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.42,0:12:48.15,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何か名前から すごそうだぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.35,0:12:49.70,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっぱ ギターだよな
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.11,0:12:51.59,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,楽しみですねえ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.22,0:12:55.28,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すっご～い 強力なメンバー 加入～！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.96,0:13:04.34,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,軽音部 軽音部？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.29,0:13:10.36,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こッ ここを抜けないと
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.62,0:13:12.98,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,軽音部に たどりつけない
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.79,0:13:16.58,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あらッ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.06,0:13:26.16,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,軽音楽部なら 音楽室よ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.71,0:13:34.88,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ここか…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.75,0:13:38.52,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,入ったばっかで言いにくいけど
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.80,0:13:40.35,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっぱり やめるって言おう
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.45,0:13:44.75,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でも 軽音部って どんな人が いるのかなあ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.18,0:13:47.18,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああん やめたいだと？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.42,0:13:50.20,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,キサマ ただでやめられると思ってるのか
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.49,0:13:52.18,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,さつがいするぞ～
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.31,0:13:56.66,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうしよう…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.39,0:14:02.51,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの あの
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.73,0:14:05.80,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ち ちッ 違います 違います…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.23,0:14:08.07,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,テンポ悪くて使えないドジっ子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.68,0:14:09.93,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何やってるの？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.23,0:14:14.22,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ビックリした
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.73,0:14:17.07,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もしかして あなたが平沢唯さん？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.21,0:14:17.96,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はッ はい
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.66,0:14:19.83,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,入部希望の
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.24,0:14:21.41,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はッ はい
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.82,0:14:25.39,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いろいろ誤解してて ごめん
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.62,0:14:27.57,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ギターがすっごく うまいんだよね
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.88,0:14:29.61,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来てくれるの待ってたよ～
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.93,0:14:32.70,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何か あらぬ尾ヒレが ついてるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.61,0:14:36.32,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,みんな～入部希望者が来たぞ～
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.64,0:14:37.35,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本当か
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.43,0:14:38.15,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まあ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.49,0:14:40.02,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ようこそ 軽音部へ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.31,0:14:42.07,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歓迎いたしますわ～
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.05,0:14:44.96,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よ～し ムギ お茶の準備だ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.16,0:14:45.79,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はい
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.82,0:14:54.15,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どッ どうしよう
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.43,0:14:56.59,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうぞ 召し上がって
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.24,0:15:02.42,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おいしい
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.49,0:15:11.07,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おいし～い
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.47,0:15:13.93,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やめるの やめようかな
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.16,0:15:16.26,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平沢さんは どんな音楽 やりたいの？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.71,0:15:19.27,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どんなバンドが好きか
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.56,0:15:21.71,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好きなギタリストは？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.97,0:15:24.12,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,えっと…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.08,0:15:26.19,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっぱ言わなきゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.57,0:15:29.18,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,実は ギターなんて弾けないって
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.47,0:15:32.48,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じ じ じ…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.62,0:15:33.82,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ジミ{\fe1\fs24\fnSimHei}·{\r}ヘンドリックス？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.30,0:15:35.12,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おお～
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.89,0:15:36.50,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いッ いえ～
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.71,0:15:38.34,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じ じ…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.48,0:15:39.50,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ジミー{\fe1\fs24\fnSimHei}·{\r}ペイジ？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.10,0:15:41.15,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああ～ッ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.82,0:15:42.12,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,違ッ じ…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.18,0:15:43.14,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ジェフ{\fe1\fs24\fnSimHei}·{\r}ベック？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.32,0:15:46.40,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ギタリストって 「じ」で始まる人 多いの？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.66,0:15:48.55,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そっか～ ジェフ{\fe1\fs24\fnSimHei}·{\r}ベックかあ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.91,0:15:49.70,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どなた？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.09,0:15:52.29,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ロックギタリストには２種類しかいない
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.71,0:15:55.48,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ジェフ{\fe1\fs24\fnSimHei}·{\r}ベックとジェフ{\fe1\fs24\fnSimHei}·{\r}ベック以外だっていわれている
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.79,0:15:59.19,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,常に 新しいサウンドを追求する 挑戦的なギタリスト
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.53,0:16:00.24,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まあ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.60,0:16:02.91,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,さっすが～シブイねえ 平沢さん
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.37,0:16:08.32,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平沢さんみたいな人が入ってくれて よかったな
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.18,0:16:12.06,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,１週間以内にあと１人 集まらなかったら
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.36,0:16:14.39,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,廃部になるところだったんです
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.81,0:16:16.60,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ほんっとに ありがと～う
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.95,0:16:18.60,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ますます言いづらいよ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.32,0:16:22.02,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でも ちゃんと言わなきゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.37,0:16:23.78,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あのッ あの
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.93,0:16:25.19,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,申し訳ないんですけど
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.47,0:16:28.69,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,実は 入部するのやめさせてくださいって 言いにきたんです
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.07,0:16:29.78,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,えッ？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.32,0:16:31.90,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ギターは弾けないし
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.40,0:16:35.26,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もっと違う楽器をやるんだと思って
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.61,0:16:37.13,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃあ 何ならできるの？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.64,0:16:39.89,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,カスタ… ハッ ハーモニカ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.04,0:16:41.50,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あッ ハーモニカならあるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.93,0:16:42.80,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吹いてみて
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.93,0:16:44.36,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ごめんなさい 吹けません
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.79,0:16:47.53,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でも ウチの部に入ろうと思ったってことは
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.82,0:16:49.90,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,音楽には興味あるってことよね
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.32,0:16:52.23,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他に入りたい部とか あるの？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.37,0:16:55.09,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ううん 特には
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.57,0:16:59.33,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せっかくのカモを ここで手放すわけにはいかないぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.41,0:17:01.88,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,廃部を免れるために
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.43,0:17:04.39,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何とか 引き止めないと
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.93,0:17:06.98,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本当に ごめんなさい じゃあ…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.35,0:17:08.04,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと待って
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.27,0:17:09.78,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もう一杯 お茶いかが？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.15,0:17:10.77,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でも…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.92,0:17:12.65,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,クッキーとマドレーヌもあるの
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.31,0:17:14.17,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餌付けた…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.45,0:17:17.85,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おいし～い
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.57,0:17:19.48,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,す すみません
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.72,0:17:21.70,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こんなにごちそうになるつもりじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.91,0:17:22.89,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいの いいの
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.37,0:17:26.46,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毎日 こうやって 一緒に お菓子を食べましょう
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.87,0:17:29.28,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何か趣旨が違ってきて… 痛ッ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.75,0:17:32.27,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平沢さん 他には どんなものが好き？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.34,0:17:36.30,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おいしいものなら何でも
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.59,0:17:37.96,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,食べ物かよ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.70,0:17:42.57,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ウチでは 休みの日とか 何して過ごしてんの？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.21,0:17:45.41,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ゴロゴロ… かな
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.54,0:17:47.91,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好きなものとか ある？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.93,0:17:51.12,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,カワイイものが好き かな
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.64,0:17:52.83,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,苦手なものは…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.22,0:17:55.56,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暑いのも 寒いのも 苦手なんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.95,0:17:58.19,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冬は コタツにこもりっきりだし
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.61,0:18:01.91,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏は 床の上をころがってばっかりいるの
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.48,0:18:03.33,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手ごわい
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.71,0:18:04.96,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一体 どうすれば…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.61,0:18:06.56,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分かりません
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.30,0:18:09.79,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あ あの… じゃあ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.54,0:18:12.39,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あッ 行かないで お願い
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.64,0:18:14.48,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ゴロゴロしてるだけで いいから
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.87,0:18:17.23,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もっと おいしいお菓子持ってきますから
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.86,0:18:24.33,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ごめんなさい 軽い気持ちで入部するなんて書いたから
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.18,0:18:31.32,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,期待させるだけさせて 何て謝ったらいいかあ…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.73,0:18:35.51,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私達こそ ごめんなさい
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.93,0:18:37.73,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無理に引き止めて 悪かったな
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.39,0:18:41.98,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃあ せめて 私達の演奏だけでも聴いていって
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.43,0:18:44.98,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,演奏してくれるの？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.30,0:18:46.61,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,食いついてきた
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.43,0:19:04.98,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ワン ツー スリー フォー
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.01,0:20:00.08,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうだった？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.46,0:20:04.05,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何ていうか すごく言葉にしにくいんだけど
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.39,0:20:04.99,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うんッ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.37,0:20:08.19,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あんまりうまくないですね
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.52,0:20:09.57,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,バッサリだあ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.21,0:20:12.68,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でも 何だか すっごく楽しそうでした
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.05,0:20:15.71,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私 この部に入部します！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.31,0:20:23.45,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,バンザ～イ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.21,0:20:27.38,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと失礼
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.16,0:20:30.70,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃあ 軽音部活動開始記念に！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.82,0:20:34.26,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああ 私のカメラ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.34,0:20:35.49,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いっくよ～ん
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.82,0:20:39.67,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あッ でも 私 全然楽器できないし
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.96,0:20:41.88,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あッ マネージャーとか どうかなあ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.16,0:20:44.13,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いや 運動部じゃないんだし
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.59,0:20:48.52,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうだ この機会にギターを始めてみたら どうかしら
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.99,0:20:51.42,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でッ でも すごく難しそうな
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.69,0:20:52.86,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大丈夫だよ～
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.18,0:20:55.88,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私達も 分かるところは教えてあげるし
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.17,0:20:58.98,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうだね
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.52,0:21:01.25,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,さっきの演奏聴いてたら
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.52,0:21:03.97,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私にも できるかもって思えてきた
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.36,0:21:06.43,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…それは よかった
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.73,0:21:11.11,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,えッ 結局 入部したんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.37,0:21:14.58,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,う～ん どうしてもって言われて～
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.87,0:21:15.60,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,マジで!?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.45,0:21:18.55,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああ マネージャーとしてとかね
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.39,0:21:21.68,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人に言われると 何か悔しい
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.05,0:21:24.18,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちゃんと メンバーとして入ったんだから
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.11,0:21:27.49,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ギター イチから教えてくれるって
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.46,0:21:32.64,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あッ ということは 新しくギター買ったりするんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.00,0:21:36.28,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うう～ん 貸してくれないのかなあ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.50,0:21:37.57,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,くれないんじゃない？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.81,0:21:41.02,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,5000円くらいで買えるよね
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.77,0:21:44.16,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こんな子 つかまされて
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.27,0:21:47.38,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大丈夫かしら… 軽音部！

Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.30,0:23:41.42,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こんにちは
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.04,0:23:44.66,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この３人が軽音部の仲間です
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.27,0:23:46.35,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,めったに出会えない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.71,0:23:50.14,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,とっても楽しくて 愉快な人達の仲間になりたかったの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.70,0:23:53.16,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ゆ… ゆい？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.37,0:23:55.43,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よっしゃ やるぞ～
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.18,0:23:59.57,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あッ みんな
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.96,0:24:01.65,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛ッ
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.51,0:24:05.25,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高校生になった私は初めて…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.47,0:24:08.26,zhengwenJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,部活を始めました！


; // CN
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.29,0:00:33.78,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐  该起床了…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.38,0:00:35.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.49,0:00:43.77,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,八  八点！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.96,0:00:45.24,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迟…迟到了迟到了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.37,0:00:46.27,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要这么着急呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.36,0:00:59.67,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迟到了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.99,0:01:04.23,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早啊  小唯
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.38,0:01:05.43,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.57,0:01:39.70,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？  看错时间了…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.72,0:01:50.68,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从今天开始
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.60,0:01:53.89,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是高中生了～
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.64,0:02:03.04,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}Chatting Now
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.12,0:02:05.86,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}ガチでカシマシ　Never Ending Girls' Talk
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.99,0:02:08.69,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}終業チャイムまで待てない
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.79,0:02:11.49,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}遅刻はしても早退はNon Non Non!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.64,0:02:15.96,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}精一杯Study After School
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.10,0:02:25.49,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}ドキドキが止まんない　フルスロットルな脳内
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.84,0:02:31.11,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}希望{\rOPC}·{\r}欲望{\rOPC}·{\r}煩悩　リボンかけて包装
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.42,0:02:36.60,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}ネタどっさり持ち寄り　New{\fscx50}　{\r}Type{\fscx50}　{\r}Version打ち込み
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.09,0:02:42.35,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}男子禁制のプリ帳　恋綴った日記帳
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.59,0:02:48.11,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}スカート丈2cm　詰めたら跳ぶよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.44,0:02:54.22,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}昨日より遠く　おとといよりオクターブ高く
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.59,0:02:55.16,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}Jumping Now
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.24,0:02:58.07,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}ガチでウルワシ　Never Ending Girls' Life
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.21,0:03:00.87,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}日々マジ　ライブだし待ったなし
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.95,0:03:03.75,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}早起きしても早寝はNon Non Non!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.92,0:03:06.67,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}目一杯Shouting　わっしょい
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.75,0:03:09.33,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}ガチでスバラシ　Never Ending Girls' Song
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.54,0:03:12.20,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}午後ティータイムには持ってこい
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.29,0:03:15.04,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}片思いでも玉砕でHere we go!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.23,0:03:19.42,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}歌えばShining After School
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.64,0:02:03.04,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}Chatting Now
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.12,0:02:05.86,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}总是吵闹　Never Ending Girls' Talk
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.99,0:02:08.69,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}直到下课铃响前都不会等待
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.79,0:02:11.49,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}迟到难免早退Non Non Non!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.64,0:02:15.96,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}竭尽全力Study After School
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.10,0:02:25.49,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}心跳不已　脑内堆满
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.84,0:02:31.11,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}希望·欲望·烦恼　用礼带包装起来
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.42,0:02:36.60,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}带来诸多NETA　贯注New Type Version
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.09,0:02:42.35,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}男子禁止的大头贴手册　汇集爱的日记本
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.59,0:02:48.11,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}裙子丈2cm　完成后就跳起来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.44,0:02:54.22,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}比昨日更远　比前日音阶更高
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.59,0:02:55.16,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}Jumping Now
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.24,0:02:58.07,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}总是尽兴　Never Ending Girls' Life
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.21,0:03:00.87,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}日日演奏　永不终结
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.95,0:03:03.75,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}早起难免早睡Non Non Non!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.92,0:03:06.67,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}放眼纵然Shouting　嘿哟
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.75,0:03:09.33,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}绝佳绝佳　Never Ending Girls' Song
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.54,0:03:12.20,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}在下午茶时间带来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.29,0:03:15.04,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}单相思也要玉碎Here we go!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.23,0:03:19.42,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}歌唱吧　Shining After School
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.12,0:03:30.96,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝贺你入学～
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.31,0:03:32.46,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请一定来网球部看看
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.75,0:03:34.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请一定来柔道部看看
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.47,0:03:35.46,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请一定来茶道部看看
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.67,0:03:36.53,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请一定来珠算部看看
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.84,0:03:37.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请一定一定…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.75,0:04:00.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯  你在嘟哝什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.38,0:04:05.55,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  和和  其实我在想该加入什么社团好…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.61,0:04:10.65,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  你还没决定吗  已经开学两周了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.79,0:04:13.25,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是可是…我是个运动白痴
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.50,0:04:16.38,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,文化系的社团也不是很了解
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.08,0:04:20.64,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去就会变成家里蹲了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.96,0:04:23.17,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是不参加社团活动就变家里蹲了啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.55,0:04:28.31,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在想想  唯从来没有参加过社团活动啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.39,0:04:28.31,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家…家…里…蹲…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.69,0:04:29.23,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扑哧！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.32,0:04:33.25,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然觉得必须要做点什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.34,0:04:38.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但到底做什么好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.73,0:04:44.73,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an2}#1　　废部!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.99,0:04:50.19,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,澪！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.83,0:04:51.54,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,律
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.67,0:04:53.11,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起去社团参观吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.41,0:04:54.51,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社团参观？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.83,0:04:56.69,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轻音部啊  轻音部
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.12,0:04:59.96,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我准备进文学部
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.12,0:04:59.96,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（日文中“文芸”是中文里“文学”的意思）
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.12,0:05:00.62,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.76,0:05:02.72,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,入部申请书都写好了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.70,0:05:06.50,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,撕
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.84,0:05:09.14,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  你在做什么啊  律
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.11,0:05:11.89,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  走吧  快点快点
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.19,0:05:13.49,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.10,0:05:17.13,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？ 废部了？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.22,0:05:20.34,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正确来说是即将废部
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.72,0:05:23.81,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前年那届的部员全都毕业了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.59,0:05:28.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是这个月里没有四人入部的话  就要废部了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.66,0:05:31.80,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…难怪音乐室里一个人都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.16,0:05:33.32,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.43,0:05:36.15,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下  马上来
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.58,0:05:39.49,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真抱歉  我等会还有音乐课
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.70,0:05:42.95,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油  轻音部
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.36,0:05:46.17,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个漂亮的老师
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.36,0:05:47.77,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在不是在说这个
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.63,0:05:54.87,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去把这些资料发给大家
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.86,0:05:59.64,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,资料…？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.74,0:06:02.31,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是是  十分抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.56,0:06:08.73,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被盯着看了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.33,0:06:10.24,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟不上调子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.72,0:06:12.39,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟…糟糕了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.43,0:06:13.46,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨手笨脚
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.77,0:06:15.30,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真…真对不起  
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.87,0:06:16.93,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.83,0:06:20.91,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天然呆…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.25,0:06:25.91,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,废部就没办法了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.29,0:06:27.85,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我去文学部了…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.32,0:06:30.92,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在一个人都没有就意味着…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.03,0:06:33.77,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我入部了就是部长了？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.83,0:06:36.20,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不错啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.63,0:06:40.46,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  刚才谈到的那个轻音部
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.90,0:06:41.88,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轻音部？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.08,0:06:43.17,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那到底是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.63,0:06:46.19,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,写成「轻松的音乐」的「轻音」
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.73,0:06:49.04,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轻松的音乐？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.66,0:06:51.69,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  轻松的音乐
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.77,0:07:00.50,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是  你打算怎么办？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.97,0:07:02.66,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等待入部志愿者
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.02,0:07:03.71,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要等啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.95,0:07:04.87,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.23,0:07:05.88,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.07,0:07:20.06,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.08,0:07:24.24,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个～我想参观一下
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.64,0:07:25.67,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.37,0:07:28.35,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,参观轻音部？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.58,0:07:30.03,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  是合唱部…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.29,0:07:32.02,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要加入轻音部吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.55,0:07:33.95,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  是合唱部…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.03,0:07:35.85,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在部员很少  所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.24,0:07:38.70,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了  绝对不会让你失望的…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.22,0:07:41.99,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么强行招人会让人家为难的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.14,0:07:45.83,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  我先走了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.12,0:07:46.84,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,澪
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.60,0:07:53.22,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候的约定…难道是骗人的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.70,0:07:57.14,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是鼓手  澪是贝司手…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.48,0:08:04.99,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直…一直组乐队…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.86,0:08:08.13,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是约好的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.46,0:08:12.35,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我们一起去看演唱会的那天…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.97,0:08:15.05,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这个
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.62,0:08:17.81,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是…这个
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.96,0:08:22.68,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时你说的话难道是骗人的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.87,0:08:24.29,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那回想是骗人的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.46,0:08:25.99,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  是这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.60,0:08:32.47,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这个了  来组乐队吧乐队
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.53,0:08:35.16,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是律在自说自话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.38,0:08:37.01,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,澪不是也说过要组吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.38,0:08:38.45,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话是这么说…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.85,0:08:40.29,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有  发展为职业级以后
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.47,0:08:42.30,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,演出费就是三七开
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.42,0:08:43.39,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别瞎编了！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.81,0:08:50.48,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉好有趣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.75,0:08:55.64,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说我只会键盘乐器  但如果不嫌弃的话就请让我加入吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.68,0:09:00.77,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万分感谢  这样只要再有一个人加入就…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.94,0:09:03.03,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…已经把我算进去了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.12,0:09:04.56,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.71,0:09:06.71,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是琴吹
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.04,0:09:08.44,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是鼓手田井中律
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.84,0:09:10.77,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是负责贝司的秋山澪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.30,0:09:13.01,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…还有就是…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.16,0:09:14.31,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉他手了！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.28,0:09:19.01,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.74,0:09:23.69,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然进了高中  总想做点什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.91,0:09:25.13,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  那就做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.06,0:09:30.28,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是不知道该做什么嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.52,0:09:32.57,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伤脑筋
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.90,0:09:37.13,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还要加一份薯条吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.41,0:09:40.37,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.48,0:09:41.65,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢惠顾
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.57,0:09:46.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.53,0:09:49.61,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是第一次来快餐店
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.89,0:09:50.70,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.23,0:09:55.48,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直希望被人问一次「还要加一份薯条吗」
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.32,0:09:59.28,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真抱歉  请开始吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.27,0:10:05.58,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  为了在这个月再找到一个部员  开始作战会议吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.89,0:10:07.31,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要做什么呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.67,0:10:10.18,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是接下去要想的～
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.86,0:10:14.51,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在入部的话  会得到很特别的特典之类啦～
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.76,0:10:15.62,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特典…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.94,0:10:17.77,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  要是会得到什么的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.22,0:10:21.36,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如说汽车啊  别墅什么的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.68,0:10:23.17,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是很厉害…但是不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.54,0:10:25.90,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像是请吃冰淇淋啦  帮忙做作业之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.30,0:10:28.16,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会有人为这个入部吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.50,0:10:29.80,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  怎么做才好呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.16,0:10:38.10,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扭咯～
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.56,0:10:40.31,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自己都觉得无聊了怎么行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.60,0:10:42.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那想点什么嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.25,0:10:45.28,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唉  我想回家
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.74,0:10:48.01,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  总之先…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.83,0:10:49.75,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一  二
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.81,0:11:00.29,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四月已经  只剩下…一周了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.07,0:11:02.89,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…谁也没来呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.74,0:11:05.47,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没组成乐队就直接废部吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.91,0:11:08.02,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那绝对不行！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.82,0:11:18.13,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轻…音乐啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.89,0:11:27.51,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小唯做得真不错呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.16,0:11:34.21,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,决定了！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.98,0:11:39.19,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,K-ON!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.63,0:11:43.59,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之我决定加入轻音乐部了！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.45,0:11:47.04,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里都做些什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.53,0:11:48.19,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道诶
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.99,0:11:52.04,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过既然叫「轻」音乐
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.26,0:11:54.40,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定都是些简单的事情啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.03,0:11:56.23,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,口笛之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.71,0:11:58.73,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种没干劲的社团算什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.46,0:12:03.36,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看  好像要组乐团哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.34,0:12:06.21,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我不会弹吉他啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.70,0:12:08.57,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你会弹些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.55,0:12:13.95,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,响板…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.02,0:12:20.71,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…很适合你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.04,0:12:22.04,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看这个
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.20,0:12:22.95,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.35,0:12:24.25,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.64,0:12:26.93,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.11,0:12:28.76,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人打算加入了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.48,0:12:32.45,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这下好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.12,0:12:37.48,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有  这套茶具虽然很漂亮  不过喝完后记得要收拾好哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.00,0:12:39.38,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好～
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.16,0:12:44.32,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好！这下不用废部了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.87,0:12:46.20,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平泽 唯
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.42,0:12:48.15,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看名字好像很厉害耶
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.35,0:12:49.70,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是吉他手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.11,0:12:51.59,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真期待呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.22,0:12:55.28,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒啦！强力团员加入啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.96,0:13:04.34,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轻音部…轻音部…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.29,0:13:12.98,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…不从这里过去  就到不了轻音部…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.79,0:13:16.58,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.06,0:13:26.16,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轻音乐部在音乐教室哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.71,0:13:34.88,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.75,0:13:38.52,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然才刚进来  难以启齿
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.80,0:13:40.35,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但还是得说我不加入
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.45,0:13:44.75,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过…轻音部里都有些怎样的人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.18,0:13:47.18,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？不干啦？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.42,0:13:50.20,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说不干就不干吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.49,0:13:52.18,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀了你！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.31,0:13:56.66,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办…！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.39,0:14:02.51,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.73,0:14:05.80,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不不不…不不不…不不不不不…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.23,0:14:08.07,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟不上调子又笨手笨脚的天然呆
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.68,0:14:09.93,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.23,0:14:14.22,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吓死我了…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.73,0:14:17.07,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫非你就是那个平泽唯同学吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.21,0:14:17.96,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  是
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.66,0:14:19.83,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是你打算加入啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.24,0:14:21.41,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…是
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.82,0:14:25.39,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思误会你了！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.62,0:14:27.57,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你弹吉他超厉害的吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.88,0:14:29.61,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都在等你啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.93,0:14:32.70,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她好像误会了什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.61,0:14:36.32,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家～新部员来咯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.64,0:14:37.35,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.43,0:14:38.15,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.49,0:14:40.02,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎加入轻音部
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.31,0:14:42.07,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,热烈欢迎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.05,0:14:44.96,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了  准备上茶
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.16,0:14:45.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好～
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.82,0:14:54.15,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎么办…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.43,0:14:56.59,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请用吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.24,0:15:02.42,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好喝～
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.49,0:15:11.07,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吃～
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.47,0:15:13.93,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是不提走人的事情好了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.16,0:15:16.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平泽同学想演奏怎样的音乐呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.71,0:15:19.27,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜欢怎样的乐队？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.56,0:15:21.71,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢的吉他手呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.97,0:15:24.12,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.08,0:15:29.18,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是得说出来  其实我根本不会弹什么吉他…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.47,0:15:32.48,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其…其…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.62,0:15:33.82,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉米·亨德雷斯（Jimi Hendrix）？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.30,0:15:35.12,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.89,0:15:38.34,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…吉…吉…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.48,0:15:39.50,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉米·佩奇（Jimmy Page）？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.10,0:15:41.15,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.82,0:15:42.12,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是…吉…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.18,0:15:43.14,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰夫·贝克（Jeff Beck）？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.32,0:15:46.40,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道有很多吉他手都是J开头吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.66,0:15:48.55,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊！是杰夫·贝克啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.91,0:15:49.70,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是哪位？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.09,0:15:55.48,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说摇滚吉他手只有两种  杰夫·贝克和杰夫·贝克以外
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.79,0:15:59.19,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永远在追求新鲜音感  极富挑战的吉他手！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.53,0:16:00.24,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.60,0:16:02.91,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然很专业啊  平泽同学
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.37,0:16:08.32,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平泽同学这样的人能加入真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.18,0:16:12.06,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我们一星期内不能再找不到一个人加入的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.36,0:16:14.39,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就要被废部了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.81,0:16:16.60,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的谢谢你！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.95,0:16:18.60,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这下越来越说不出口了…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.32,0:16:22.02,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可不讲清楚又不行…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.37,0:16:25.19,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…真的很抱歉！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.47,0:16:28.69,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际上我是想来说我不打算加入了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.07,0:16:29.78,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.32,0:16:35.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我根本不会弹吉他  本以为是演奏别的乐器…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.61,0:16:37.13,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你会什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.64,0:16:39.89,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,响…口琴！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.04,0:16:42.80,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  口琴这里有哦  吹吹看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.93,0:16:44.36,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  我不会吹！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.79,0:16:49.90,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过  既然打算加入我们社团  说明你还是对音乐感兴趣的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.32,0:16:52.23,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有其它想参加的社团吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.37,0:16:55.09,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…没什么特别想的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.57,0:16:59.33,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘴边的鸭子怎么能让她飞了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.41,0:17:01.88,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了免于被废部！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.43,0:17:04.39,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要劝她回头
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.93,0:17:06.98,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真对不起  再见
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.35,0:17:08.04,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.27,0:17:09.78,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要再添一杯茶呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.15,0:17:10.77,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.92,0:17:12.65,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还有饼干和松糕哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.31,0:17:14.17,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下饵了…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.45,0:17:17.85,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好吃～
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.57,0:17:21.70,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对…对不起！本来不想吃你们这么多的…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.91,0:17:22.89,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事没事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.37,0:17:26.46,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以后我们每天这样一起吃点心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.87,0:17:29.28,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么觉得偏离主题了…好痛…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.75,0:17:32.27,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平泽同学  你还有什么其它喜欢的？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.34,0:17:36.30,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吃的东西我都喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.59,0:17:37.96,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…就惦记着吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.70,0:17:42.57,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平常放假你在家都怎么过呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.21,0:17:45.41,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闲呆着…吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.54,0:17:47.91,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜欢什么东西呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.93,0:17:51.12,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可爱的东西…吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.64,0:17:52.83,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.22,0:17:55.56,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太热太冷我都不喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.95,0:17:58.19,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冬天都窝在桌炉里面
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.61,0:18:01.91,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏天就趴在地板上无所事事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.48,0:18:03.33,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真棘手…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.71,0:18:04.96,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,究竟怎么办才好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.61,0:18:06.56,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.30,0:18:09.79,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…那个…那我就…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.54,0:18:12.39,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  别走！求求你
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.64,0:18:14.48,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只要在这里闲呆着就好啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.87,0:18:17.23,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再去拿些好吃的点心来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.86,0:18:24.33,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起…随随便便就交上申请书…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.18,0:18:31.32,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还让你们这么期待…我该怎样道歉才好…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.73,0:18:35.51,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们才应该道歉…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.93,0:18:37.73,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  强留你下来…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.39,0:18:41.98,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  至少听听我们的演奏吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.43,0:18:44.98,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为我演奏吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.30,0:18:46.61,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上钩了…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.43,0:19:04.98,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,One  Two  Three  Four
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.01,0:20:00.08,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.46,0:20:04.05,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么说呢…我觉得很难用语言表达…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.39,0:20:04.99,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.37,0:20:08.19,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是很精彩呢！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.52,0:20:09.57,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好直接！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.21,0:20:12.68,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过感觉很有趣的样子！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.05,0:20:15.71,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要加入这个社团！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.31,0:20:23.45,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万岁！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.21,0:20:27.38,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失礼～
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.16,0:20:30.70,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么作为轻音部活动开始纪念
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.82,0:20:34.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  我的相机…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.34,0:20:35.49,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要拍咯～
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.82,0:20:39.67,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  可我完全不会乐器
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.96,0:20:41.88,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  当经纪人怎么样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.16,0:20:44.13,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃  这又不是运动部
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.59,0:20:48.52,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  就借此机会开始学吉他怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.99,0:20:51.42,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可这个好像很难…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.69,0:20:55.88,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事啦  我们知道的都会教你啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.17,0:20:58.98,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.52,0:21:03.97,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听过刚才的演奏  我有种我也可以做到的感觉呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.36,0:21:06.43,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…那太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.73,0:21:11.11,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  最后你还是加入了？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.37,0:21:14.58,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  她们一定要我加入嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.87,0:21:15.60,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.45,0:21:18.55,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…是做经纪人什么的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.39,0:21:21.68,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被别人这么说感觉真不好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.05,0:21:24.18,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是作为正式成员加入的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.11,0:21:27.49,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她们说会从头教我弹吉他哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.46,0:21:32.64,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  那么说你要买把新吉他了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.00,0:21:36.28,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…不知道会不会借我呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.50,0:21:37.57,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.81,0:21:41.02,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,5000日元左右应该能买到吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.77,0:21:47.38,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓这孩子去做部员能行吗…轻音部！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.64,0:22:14.00,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}Please don't say“You are lazy”
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.23,0:22:16.63,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}だって本当はcrazy
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.88,0:22:21.92,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}白鳥達はそう　見えないところでバタ足するんです
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.21,0:22:27.23,EDJ2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}本能に従順 忠実　翻弄も重々承知
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.54,0:22:32.71,EDJ2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}前途洋々だし…だからたまに休憩しちゃうんです
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.67,0:22:43.43,EDJ2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}近道あればそれが王道　はしょれる翼もあれば上等
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.13,0:22:53.17,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}ヤバ 爪割れた　グルーで補修した
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.38,0:22:58.50,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}それだけでなんか達成感
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.68,0:23:03.80,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}大事なのは自分　かわいがること
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.97,0:23:09.78,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}自分を愛さなきゃ　他人も愛せない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.37,0:23:12.97,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}Please don't say“You are lazy”
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.26,0:23:15.58,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}だって本当はcrazy
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.85,0:23:20.94,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}能ある鷹はそう　見えないとこにピック隠すんです
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.16,0:23:26.24,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}想像に一生懸命　現実は絶体絶命
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.53,0:23:31.96,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}発展途中だし…だから不意にピッチ外れるんです
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.64,0:22:14.00,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}Please don't say“You are lazy”
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.23,0:22:16.63,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}因为其实是crazy
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.88,0:22:21.92,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}白鸟们在暗处浅打水
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.21,0:22:27.23,EDC2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}忠实顺从本能　明知重重颠簸
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.54,0:22:32.71,EDC2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}前途光明…所以稍事休息吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.67,0:22:43.43,EDC2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}近道即王道　折翼更上等
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.13,0:22:53.17,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}利爪破裂　以胶修补
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.38,0:22:58.50,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}如此就有成就感
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.68,0:23:03.80,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}怜惜自己很重要
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.97,0:23:09.78,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}不爱自己何谈爱他人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.37,0:23:12.97,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}Please don't say“You are lazy”
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.26,0:23:15.58,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}因为其实是crazy
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.85,0:23:20.94,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}能乐者敛其锋芒
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.16,0:23:26.24,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}拼命想像　现实却一筹莫展
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.53,0:23:31.96,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1}还在发展途中…所以会意外地走音
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.30,0:23:41.42,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家好
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.04,0:23:44.66,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这三位就是轻音部的伙伴们
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.27,0:23:50.14,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想和这些可遇不可求的愉快的人成为伙伴
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.70,0:23:53.16,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯…唯？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.37,0:23:55.43,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好！上吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.18,0:23:59.57,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  大家
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.96,0:24:01.65,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…痛
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.51,0:24:05.25,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成为高中生的我第一次…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.47,0:24:08.26,zhengwen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,参加社团了！
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.15,0:24:09.66,title2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,0)}#2　　乐器!


